icanhazchat.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

IHAZACHAT Inc ("icanhazchat", "we" or "us") respects and takes the privacy of the visitors, users and members of its website (www.icanhazchat.com) (the "Website") very seriously. We provide this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information that we receive and collect on the Website. 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the provisions of the Terms of Service, and your use of the Website and any personal information you provide us with, are subject to the Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy. BY USING THE WEBSITE YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE Terms of Service AND THIS PRIVACY POLICY, REGARDLESS OF YOUR FAILURE TO READ THEM. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy or with the Terms of Service, please do not use the Website. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in the Terms of Service. 

You should be aware that when you share or broadcast personal information in public areas of the Website, such as channels and chat rooms, this information becomes publicly available and can be seen, used and gathered by others, and therefore is not subject to this Privacy Policy. We urge you to exercise good judgment when sharing personal information in these forums. You should also be aware that when you broadcast, post, submit or upload any content or messages on the Website, your User Name is displayed to other users and visitors, and other members can contact you and post comments. Any User Generated Content may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 

### What Information do we collect and for what purpose?

Our main goals in collecting information are to provide and improve the Website and its services, and to administer the membership of registered users. 

We collect three types of information from the Website: 

personal information - Personal Information is any piece of information about an identifiable individual. In order to enjoy and use some of the features of the Website (such as broadcasting your own TV show, participating in contests etc.), you will have to register with the website and become a member. During the registration process you will be asked to provide us with certain Personal Information like your name, email address, postal address etc. that are required to operate these features and services. By voluntarily providing this Personal Information to us, by sending us a comment or suggestion, by becoming a member or by entering a contest that is posted on the website, you will be consenting to the collection, use and distribution of your personal information by us, for the purposes specified in the Privacy Policy. Please note that you are under no obligation to provide us with any Personal Information and can access and enjoy many parts of the Website without providing us with any personal information. 

We use your Personal Information for several purposes: (1) to enable you to use certain features, services and functionalities of the Website; (2) to contact you, respond to questions and comments you may send us, and to provide you with newsletters or other information about programming, special offers or services on the Website; (3) to operate and maintain the Website and its services, including moderating and running channels and chat-rooms; (4) to provide you with marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. In addition, we may combine your Personal Information and/or certain non-identifying information and aggregate it with information collected from other users of the Website, in order to better design the Website and services, by analyzing and evaluating the way the Website is being used. We may disclose such aggregated information as provided hereinafter. 

Anonymous Information about visits in the Website - When you visit the Website (whether as a member or as a visitor), information about your visit (such as how you navigate the site) may be collected and stored. This information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser and platform type, the length of your visit, the date and time of your visit, the pages you viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, and the websites you visit before and after leaving the Website. It does not include any personally identifiable information such as your name, e-mail address or telephone number. 

We use this information mainly to monitor and analyze the aggregate use of the Website and its services, and for the Website’s technical administration. As mentioned above, we may aggregate such data (alone or with Personal Information) in order to better design the Website and services. 

Cookies - Like many other websites, we use "cookies" to collect information and to tailor the Website to the needs and interests of its members and visitors. A cookie is a small entry-in text file that is transferred from the Website’s servers to your computer’s hard drive, and uniquely identifies your browser. Cookies can only be read by the server that sent them to you, and cannot read data from your hard drive. The Website uses two types of Cookies for two purposes: (1) Persistent cookies that remain on your hard drive after you close your browser, and are used to save some information about you and your preferences (e.g. your registration ID) for future visits to the Website. (2) Session cookies that are temporary and are deleted from your hard drive after you close your browser. 

We use cookies to: (1) remember some information (e.g. registration ID) so that you will not have to re-enter it during each visit to the Website; (2) provide you with custom, personalized content and information; (3) monitor the effectiveness of marketing campaigns; and (4) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc. 

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to alert you before accepting a cookie. However, you may not be able to access some areas, or use some functionalities of the Website, which require cookies. 

### Disclosure and Sharing of Information

Compliance with Laws and Law enforcement - IHAZACHAT may disclose any and all information, including Personal Information, if it is required to do so by (or in its sole and good-faith discretion, believes that such action is necessary to comply with) any applicable law or regulation, or an order of a court or other governmental body having jurisdiction. IHAZACHAT may also disclose your Personal Information if in its sole and good-faith discretion believes that such disclosure is necessary to enforce the Terms of Service, take precautions against possible liability, investigate and defend itself against any yours or any third-party claims or allegations, protect its property and rights (including the security or integrity of the Website), protect the property, rights or safety of any third party, and/or prevent or stop any illegal or unethical activity. Please note that aggregate information and metrics about the Website (such as number of users), but not Personal Information, may be disclosed to the public, in order to comply with applicable securities laws and regulations. 

Multi-site harassment - if you are harassing ICHC users on other sites we may share information with the admins of those sites. 

Sale, Merger or Acquisition - IHAZACHAT may sell, transfer, assign or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including information it has collected, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of assets, change of control or in the unfortunate event of bankruptcy. In such case, your Personal Information may become subject to a different privacy policy. 

### Review, Amending and Deleting Information

You may review, update, amend or delete your Personal Information, at any time, by the update profile form. 

### Data Security

We are very concerned with safeguarding your Personal Information. We employ commercially reasonable physical, administrative, and electronic security measures to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, and to ensure the integrity and security of your Personal Information. Please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

If we learn of a breach of the security, then we shall take any legally required disclosures and notification of such breach, via email or by posting a notice on the Website, in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay. 

You should be aware that your information may be transferred to and/or maintained on, computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. 

### Links to other websites and Advertisements

The Website may contain links to third party websites and advertisements. If you choose to visit such linked websites or advertisements, by clicking on a link or a banner, you will be directed to that third party’s website. The fact that such links and advertisements are posted and presented on the Website is not an endorsement or representation of any kind, of those websites or their privacy policies and practices. We assume no responsibility in any way for the privacy policies and practices of other websites and encourage you to review the privacy policies of those linked websites before using them. 

We may use third-parties, known as ad-servers, to serve and target advertisements, promotions and other marketing messages, in connection with the Website. Such third parties may use technologies (such as cookies) to monitor the effectiveness of marketing campaigns. We do not control the activities of such third parties, assume no responsibility in any way for their privacy policies and practices, and encourage you to review their privacy policies. We do not provide any such third-parties with any Personal Information, without your consent. However, you should be aware that your response to certain advertisements or campaigns, targeted at specific audiences, may reveal personal information about yourself (such as age or area of residence). Such third parties may also collect and use non-identifying information about your usage of the Website. 

**_March 13th 2013_ : accounts that are not-hearted may see ads from 3rd parties. If this includes you and you would like to disable tracking for your current browser, see http://www.lijit.com/choices&rsquo; target=’_blank’>Ad Choices - Opt Out Cookie to opt-out.**

### Children

This Website is not directed to and intended for minors under 13 and does not knowingly collect Personal Information and other types of information about minors. If you are under 13 years of age, please do not use this Website. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information, he or she should contact using the contact link. 

### International users and transfer of information

You should be aware that the Website intended for and directed to residents of the United States. If you access the Website from any other country, in which the laws governing the collection, use, or disclosure of personal information are different than the United States laws, please be advised that your usage of the Website is governed by the United States laws. 

You should also be aware that your Personal Information and other data will be stored and processed in the United States and may be subject to the laws of these jurisdictions 

### Amendments of this Privacy Policy

IHAZACHAT reserves the right to amend, update or modify, at any time, this Privacy Policy without notice, and it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy for any amendments. Such amendments, updates and modifications shall be effective immediately upon posting them on the Website. Your use of the Website following any amendment of this Privacy Policy will signify your assent to and acceptance of its revised terms. We recommend that you check the Website periodically for any such amendments to this Privacy Policy. We further recommend that you print a copy of this Privacy Policy for future reference. 

If you have any questions or comments with regard to this Privacy Policy, your Personal Information or any other related issue, please contact us using the contact link.
